<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="home.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<content>
   <details>
      <title>UEFA Euro 2016</title>
      <location>France</location>
      <dates>
         <start_date>10-June-2016</start_date>
         <end_date>10-july-2016</end_date>
      </dates>
   </details>
   <description>
      <intro >The 2016 UEFA European Championship, commonly referred to as UEFA Euro 2016, will be the 15th edition of the UEFA European Championship, 
             the quadrennial international men's football championship of Europe organized by UEFA. It is scheduled to be held in France from 10 
             June to 10 July 2016. Spain are two-time defending champions.For the first time, the European Championship final tournament will be 
             contested by 24 teams, having been expanded from the 16-team format used since 1996. Under this new format, the finalists will contest 
             a group stage consisting of six groups of four teams, followed by a knockout stage including three rounds and the final. 19 teams joined 
             France who qualified automatically as hosts. A two-legged play-off in November 2015 decided the last four spots at the final tournament.
             France was chosen as the host on 28 May 2010, after a bidding process in which they beat Italy and Turkey for the right to host the 
             2016 finals. The matches will be played in ten stadia in ten cities: Bordeaux, Lens, Lille, Lyon, Marseille, Nice, Paris, Saint-Denis, 
             Saint-Étienne, and Toulouse. It will be the third time that France hosts the tournament, after the inaugural tournament in 1960 and the 
             1984 finals. The French team have won the European Championship twice: in 1984 and 2000.
      </intro>
      <teams>The 14 European Championship tournaments have been won by nine different national teams: Germany and Spain each have won three titles, 
             France has two titles, and Soviet Union, Italy, Czechoslovakia, Netherlands, Denmark and Greece have won one title each. To date, Spain 
             are the only side in history to have won consecutive titles, doing so in the 2008 and 2012 editions. It is the 2nd most watched football 
             tournament in the world after the World Cup. Euro 2012 final was watched by a global audience of around 300 million. The most recent 
             championship, co-hosted by Poland and Ukraine in 2012, was won by Spain, who beat Italy 4–0 at the final in Kiev.
      </teams>
      <winner>The winning team earns the right to compete at the 2017 FIFA Confederations Cup hosted by Russia.</winner>
   </description>
   <pictures>
      <image caption="Image1" source="ireland.jpg" />
      <image caption="Image2" source="germany.jpg" />
      <image caption="Image3" source="france.jpg" />
      <image caption="Image4" source="england.jpg" />
   </pictures>
</content>